## Guilherme Patriota

#### **Product Data Analyst**



H4V 2Y2 - Montréal/QC



+1 (438) 926-0872



linkedin.com/in/guilhermepatriota



guipatriota@gmail.com

## About me —

Guilherme Patriota is a fast learner professional who works as Data Science Professor and Electrical Engineer with a Masters in AI in search of an opportunity to work in his areas of interest. Working as a University Professor in the Computer Engineering and Data Science courses since 2016 I know I can make the difference at your company to achieve financial goals and make the crypto world a trusted place to trade money again.

# Skills

Team Work, Analytical Mind, Teaching

AWS, RDS, Linux Shell, Docker

Eletronics, IoT, MQTT, Kafka

Hbase, Redis, MongoDB, Elasticsearch

Python, AI, Logic, C++, R, Skala

DBA, SQL DDL, MySQL, NoSQL

Big Data, Hadoop, Spark

English, French, Portuguese

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

#### Interests

Cryptocurrencies; Data Science; Big Data

### Education

2013-2016	MBA in Healthcare Improuvments into medical equipments maintenance.	FGV/Brazil
2009-2011	M.Sc. Electrical Engineer  AI with electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2002-2006	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer Electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2004-2004	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer  Sandwitch degree in Electrical Engineer - Electronics	ENSPS/France

#### Experience

since 2016	University Professor University Professor in the Software Enging and Data Science courses at UNIN Center in Brasil and Educator at AWS A	TER - International University
2020-2021	New Technologies Developer Develop eletronics and software for ne ucts. Manage projects database. Mana	

2018-2020	3D Printer Engineer.	GS3D
	Build, repair end configure 3d printer and 3d modeling.	

2012-2018 Clinical Engineer. Several Hospitals in Brazil
Maintain and repair medical and non medical equipments. Manage
Datacenter. Mantain hospiatl and pacients database secure and online
24/7. Manage technician and IT teams.

#### Volunteer Experience

2020	Volunteer GS3D
	Development, 3D printing and delivery of 500 face shields for donation
	to healthcare professionals in Curitiba during the first 6 months of the
	COVID-19 pandemic in Brazil.

2009-2010 Brazilian Scouts Monitor GEUJ - Grupo Escoteiro União Juventus Organize activities for Pionneers (young people between 15 and 17 years old) assisting them in developing their physical, spiritual, intellectual, social and affective potential.

## Complementary Studies

2020	Knowledge discovery in database and datamining. UFPR/Brazil	60h
2020	Data Science foundations.  Aldeia Coworking/Brazil	32h
2020	Introduction to computer programming using python.  MITx	9 weeks
2020	AI fundamentals.  Data Science Academy	8h
2020	Datascience 2.0.	8h

## Portfolio

GitHub github.com/guipatriota

Data Science Academy